Resolving dependencies...
Downloading packages...
  cupertino_icons 1.0.9 (2.0.0 available)
  material_color_utilities 0.13.0 (0.13.1 available)
  test_api 0.7.12 (0.7.14 available)
  vector_math 2.4.0 (2.4.3 available)
Got dependencies!
4 packages have newer versions incompatible with dependency constraints.
Try `flutter pub outdated` for more information.
00:00 +0: loading E:/niaverp-root/niaverp/test/application/gst_posting_engine_test.dart
00:00 +0: intra-state sale posts balanced Output CGST/SGST arms Dr Party / Cr Sales / Cr taxes, Dr = Cr, pos recorded
00:00 +1: intra-state sale posts balanced Output CGST/SGST arms odd-paise bases use separate halves, never a split total
00:00 +2: intra-state sale posts balanced Output CGST/SGST arms round-off runs once on net + tax with Dr = Cr
00:00 +3: inter-state purchase posts Dr Input IGST Cr Party / Dr Purchases / Dr IGST, pos recorded
00:00 +4: multi-rate invoices aggregate per line 18% + 5% lines sum independently
00:00 +5: ship-to vs bill-to (CA Q2) third-party direction uses the bill-to state
00:00 +6: ship-to vs bill-to (CA Q2) without direction, the ship-to state decides
00:00 +7: blocks refuse loudly and write nothing taxable registered buyer with bad GSTIN blocks
00:00 +8: blocks refuse loudly and write nothing taxable reverse charge, export, services block
00:00 +9: blocks refuse loudly and write nothing taxable missing tax ledger names the role and refuses
00:00 +10: blocks refuse loudly and write nothing taxable exempt voucher with a rated line blocks; tax-free posts clean
00:00 +11: cancel and returns mirror tax cancel writes mirror arms for every tax line
00:00 +12: cancel and returns mirror tax sales return reverses the output sides
00:00 +13: cancel and returns mirror tax purchase return reverses the input sides
00:00 +14: locked periods refuse tax postings too post into a locked period fails with the lock message
00:00 +15: All tests passed!
